I crossed the street to avoid meeting him, but he saw me and came running towards me.
It was no use pretending that I had not seen him, so I waved to him.
I never enjoy meeting Nigel Dykes.
He never has anything to do.
No matter how busy you are, he always insists on coming with you.
I had to think of a way of preventing him from following me around all morning.
'Hello, Nigel,' I said.
'Fancy meeting you here!'
'Hi, Elizabeth,' Nigel answered.
'I was just wondering how to spend the morning -- until I saw you.
You're not busy doing anything, are you?'
'No, not at all,' I answered.
'I'm going to...'
'Would you mind my coming with you?'
he asked, before I had finished speaking.
'Not at all,' I lied, 'but I'm going to the dentist.'
'Then I'll come with you,' he answered.
'There's always plenty to read in the waiting room!'